I just want to move this place fast.
我只是想赶快搬到这里.
I'll call you tomorrow.
我明天给你打电话。
Edie, wait.
Edie，等等
It's so incomprehensible to me that Edie Britt would try to destroy us.
我真不能理解Edie Britt要毁了我们。
For 5 grand, she's hurt.
5个,她受伤
10 grand, she's gone.
10个,她就死了
Some neighbors hired help...
一些邻居被雇来帮忙...
how am I supposed to pull off a formal dinner with no warning?
我怎么能想到会举行一个没有预告的正式晚餐?
I don't know.
我不知道啊.
Some just couldn't stop.
有些人不能停止.
Smile, Gabrielle.
微笑,Gabrielle
And one...
还有一个...
didn't stop in time.
没有结束
Oh, Andrew, I need your help, honey.
哦,亲爱的,Andrew,我需要你的帮助.
Mama?
妈妈?
There is a widely read book that tells us everyone is a sinner.
有一本流行的书告诉我们每个人都是罪人.
Of course, not everyone who reads this book feels guilt over the bad things they do,
当然了,不是每个人看了这书都对他们所做的坏事感到愧疚
but Bree Van De Kamp did.
但是Bree Van De Kamp就觉得.
In fact, Bree had spent most of her life feeling guilty.
事实上,布雷对她这辈子做的很多事都感到内疚.
As a child, she felt guilty about not getting straight A's.
当她还是个小孩的时候,她就为了没有一排A而羞愧
As a teenager, she felt guilty about letting her boyfriend go to second base.
等到青年的时候,她又为了让她男朋友上2垒而难受.
As a newlywed, she felt guilty about taking three weeks to get out her thank-you cards.
成了个新娘的时候,她又为花三个星期弄感谢卡而愧疚
But she knew the transgressions of her past
但是她知道她过去做的错事
were nothing compared with the sin she was about to commit.
是不能跟她要坦白的罪过相比的.
Can't we just go to the police and tell them it was an accident?
难道我们就不能去警察局跟他们说那是个意外?
This wasn't some simple DUI.
这可不是什么简单的二重唱啊.
Not only was your brother drinking, Andrew left the scene of the crime.
你哥不只喝了酒,Andrew还在现场留下证据了啊
That makes it a hit-and-run.
所以才逃的啊
Maybe I could go to Canada.
或许我应该去加拿大
You know, until the statute of limitations is up.
你知道,得到法定时效实行之后
You really think mom and dad are going to foot the bill while you go moose hunting for seven years?
你真的认为爸妈只是在你去打驼鹿的 7年里签签支票吗?
If Carlos's mother dies, there is no statute of limitations.
如果Carlos的妈妈死了的话, 就没有法定时效了
Right, because then it's murder.
是啊,但是那会变成谋杀
Shut up!
别说了!
You shut up.
你才别说了呢!
How could it be murder? It was an accident!
那怎么可能是谋杀,只是意外!
We have to get rid of the car.
我们必须扔了这车
But we can't sell it.
但是我们不能卖
The police might find it, and there could be DNA.
警察会找到的,会有DNA在那里
We'll take the car to a bad part of town,
我们得把车弄到城里最坏的地方.
we'll leave the keys in the ignition and the doors unlocked.
我们把钥匙插在上面门也不要锁.
If the police don't find it, we'll get the insurance money, and if they do,
如果警察找不着这车,我们就可以 拿到保险金,但是如果他们找到了
it wasn't in our possession.
这车就不属于我们了
Anyone could have hit Mrs. Solis.
谁都可能撞了Solis
That sounds good.
那倒不错
Bree, are you sure?
Bree,你确定吗?
Our son could spend the rest of his life in jail.
我们的儿子就要在监狱里度过他的余生.
I won't allow that.
我决不允许那样
Bree knew what she was about to do was wrong,
Bree知道她所要做的事是不对的.
but like most sinners, she would worry about her guilt tomorrow.
但是像很多有罪的人一样,她明天才担心犯的错。
Well, everybody should go wash up.
好了,大家去洗盘子吧
We're having pancakes for breakfast.
我们会吃煎饼当早餐
Episode 8 : Guilty
第8集: 有罪的
Not since my own suicide had violence intruded upon the serenity of life on Wisteria Lane
原来我个人的自杀举动也使 Wisteria巷子平静的生活受到了暴力干扰
in such a conspicuous fashion.
还这么明显的样子.
Needless to say, my friends attacked the problem head-on.
不用说,我的朋友们来帮我解决 这个迎面的问题
Susan brought the trash bags,
Susan带来了垃圾袋
and Bree brought the industrial-strength solvent.
Bree也把工业溶解剂带来了
Whoo. That stuff is strong.
哦,这东西太冲了
It has to be.
它必须这样
I don't want Gabrielle and Carlos coming home to this ugly reminder in front of their house.
我不想让Gabrielle和Carlos 回家的时候在房子前面看到这个丑陋的东西
So has anyone been over there?
那有人检查过吗?
Julie and I went over this morning.
Julie和我今天早上检查了
How's Juanita doing?
Juanita怎么样了?
She's been in a coma ever since she came out of the E.R.
她从急诊室出来就一直昏迷着
Nobody knows when, or even if, she'll wake up.
没人知道什么时候,有或者可能,她会醒过来
This is awful. Carlos must be just devastated.
太可怕了.Carlos会受多大的打击啊!
I hope she wakes up soon. Maybe she can tell us who was driving that car.
我希望她很快醒过来,可能她还会告诉我们谁开的车
We can only hope.
我们只能希望了
Slow down, you jerk! This is a residential neighborhood!
慢点!你这个急性子!这是在居住区!
Wow, that's quite a pitching arm you've got there.
WOW,你那样做的时候可是个很好的投掷动作啊
It  pisses me off. I've got four kids, you know?
我真气死了,我有4个孩子,你知道吗?
I was up all night reading statistics on line.
我整个晚上都得起来在网上看统计
1 out of every 4 traffic accidents happens on residential streets.
每4个交通事故都有一个发生在居住区的街道上
I hope whoever hit Juanita gets put away for life.
我希望不管是谁撞了Juanita都得被关进监狱
Don't you think that's a little bit extreme?
你难道不认为那有一点极端吗?
An innocent woman gets hit by a car and the driver just takes off?
一个无辜的女人被一辆车幢了而司机却逃跑了
I don't think it's extreme.
我不认为它极端
You should go home and get some rest, eat something.
你应该回家休息一下,吃点东西
You  have a ton of messages from work. Tanaka called, said it was urgent.
你有一吨的工作留言,Tanaka打来的,说是紧急的事
Carlos, I can stay here with your mother.
Carlos,我可以在这陪你妈妈
I need to be here if she wakes up.
如果她醒了我必须在这里
You can't go on like this.
你不能再这样继续下去了
You have to take care of yourself.
你得照顾好自己
What if she dies?
如果她死了怎么办?
People slip into comas all the time and never come out.
人如果一直陷入昏迷就不会醒了
Don't say that.
别说那个了
We need to stay positive.
我们要有积极的心态
Mr. and Mrs. Solis?
Solis先生和夫人?
John.
John
Is it okay if I come in?
我可以进来吗?
Of course.
当然可以
Mr. Solis, uh...
Solis先生,恩....
I'm so sorry this happened.
我对发生的事感到抱歉
It means a lot that you came.
你来了就很好了
Look,  I think I'm going to go down to the chapel and pray.
我想我现在该去小礼拜堂祈祷
You want to come?
你要来吗?
Um, no.
哦,不了
I think I will stay here with mama.
我想我要留在这陪妈妈
Is it all right if I come?
我去的话可以吗?
Of course.
当然了
We need all the prayers we can get.
所有的祈祷者都能来
Mrs. Solis, it's time for her sponge bath.
Solis夫人,现在要用海绵给她擦身了
Come again?
再说一次?
Sometimes family members prefer to administer sponge baths themselves.
有些时候家里人会希望自己 帮亲人做这些事情
I  think I'll pass.
我想我不必了
Martha.
Where's your purse?
你的钱包呢?
Over there. Why?
在那啊,怎么了?
What are you doing?
你在干吗?
I am taking back the $40 that you stole out of my purse.
我要把你从我的钱包里偷的40美圆拿回来
Edie.
Edie
We both know you did it. Now hand it over!
我们都知道你做了,现在要还给我了
I have taken nothing from your purse.
我没在你钱包里拿任何东西
And if you're missing money, I'd ask one of those strange men you parade through here at all hours.
如果我能偷你的钱， 我就会把你的那些猛男也一起拿来了
I am not going to apologize for having a healthy sex life.
我不会为过着健康的性生活而道歉
Healthy?
健康?
I'm going to have to burn every sheet you've touched.
我要把你碰过的所有床单都烧了
I want my money.
我要我的钱
And I want those nonfat peach yogurts.
而且我要那些脱脂的桃子酸奶
They didn't just walk out of that fridge by themselves.
他们可不会自己从冰箱里走出去.
Well, you can deduct it from the $40 that you're going to give me now.
好,那你可以把那从40美圆里减掉, 你现在可以给我了
You're my best friend.
你是我最好的朋友
Why would I steal from you?
为什么我要偷你的?
It's no secret that you've been having financial problems.
你有经济问题不是秘密
I hear you bitching on the phone to your bank.
我听见你在电话里骂银行
That's it.
那是
I can put up with your debauchery and your food theft, but I will not tolerate spying.
我可以忍受你的放荡和偷食, 但是不能忍受被监视
I want you out.
你给我出去
You don't mean that.
你不是真的吧
Oh, yes, I do.
是的,我是
I'm leaving tomorrow to visit my sister for a few days.
我明天会离开几天去看我姐姐
I want you gone by the time I get back.
我希望我回来的时候你已经不在了
I'll do you one better.
我会做个更好的
I will leave today.
我今天就走
I hope this works.
我希望这管用
My sleep cycle is totally out of whack.
我的睡眠循环严重的失调了
I'm up all night, and then dozing off during the day.
我夜里一直醒着,然后白天一直打瞌睡
Trust me. This'll do the trick.
相信我,这会有帮助的
In fact, you should be feeling more relaxed already.
事实上,你应该觉得已经很放松了
You know, you're right.
你知道,你是对的
Boys, I can hear you out there. Now be quiet.
男孩们,我可以听见你们在外面,现在安静
Just sit there and color.
只要坐在那然后画画
Now  is not a good time to be moving.
现在不是动的好时候
Right. Sorry.
是啊，对不起
Just block everything out
只要把所有的事都关在外面
and let it go.
然后让它去吧！
Imagine that you're in a forest.
想象一下你在一个森林里
There's a babbling brook nearby,
附近有条潺潺的小溪
and the wind is just coming through the trees.
风正从树中吹过来
Mommy.
妈妈
Parker.
Parker
I don't know --
我不知道
ow -- what you think you're doing,
哦,你认为你在干吗
but put that back where it belongs.
但是把它们放回原位
Sorry.
对不起
You were saying something about wind.
你说到一些有关风的东西
I was just creating a soothing image.
我正在描述一个让人安心的画面
Oh, for the love of god.
哦,上帝啊
Knock it off, you little monsters.
停,你们这些小怪物
Mrs. Scavo, please lie down.
Scavo夫人,请躺下
We need to finish this.
我们必须完成它
Look, I'm on my last nerve, so I'm going to level with you here.
我现在鼓起我最后的勇气, 希望我能和你一起坚持到底
I've screwed up my entire system by taking my kids' A.D.D. medication.
我用我孩子的A.D.D药物治疗 来使自己整个的振作起来
Yeah, that's right. You heard me.
对.你听见了.
I plan to stop, but right now, I need to sleep,
我决定要停止,但是现在,我要睡觉.
and I need more than a few crappy needles, so what do you got?
而且我需要比这些没用的 针更多的东西,你弄到什么了
I'm not licensed to write prescriptions.
我没被授权开药啊
I know you're not.
我知道你没
This will put you right to sleep.
这个可以让你立刻睡着.
It's a very powerful herbal remedy.
这是一个非常有效的草药
Now, promise me you're going to use it judiciously.
现在,答应我你会理智的用它
Sure. Whatever.
好的,不管怎样
Knock, knock.
嘿嘿
Hey, come on in.
嘿,进来
You're a mess.
你一团糟啊
I-I'm tearing out these leaky pipes in the upstairs bathroom.
我在楼上的洗手间把这些渗漏管给扯下来
Wall to wall rotten wood.
墙和墙之间的腐烂的木头
Hmm, sounds like a job.
恩..听起来是个活
So Julie said that you came by before?
所以Julie说你之前就去过了?
Um, yeah. Uh...
恩...
I was thinking about driving up to the Germani Vineyard tomorrow for this wine tasting, and, uh...
我本来在想明天开到Germani Vineyard 去参加品酒,..而且...
What time do you want me to be ready?
你想让我什么时候准备好?
About 6:00.
大概6点
6:00 is good.
6点很好
All right.
那好
You know, I thought maybe afterwards, we could have a little dinner, maybe some dancing.
你知道,我想可能然后,我们可以吃点晚餐,然后跳舞
Sounds great.
听起来很不错啊！
Um, you do know that it's, like, a 2-hour drive up there,
恩.你知道那个，大概两小时开到那吧.
and isn't that kind of late to be coming back?
而且回来还不会太晚
I thought if, you know, worse came to worst, we could grab a room.
我想如果,你知道,最坏我们就找间房
Oh?
哦?
Like a hotel room?
宾馆吗?
Yeah, as a last resort.
恩,这是最后的办法
Of course. Of course, yes.
当然. 当然
So  maybe we should make reservations. You know, just in case.
所以我们应该以防万一预定一下
Yeah, I found some hotels online. Let me get the printout.
是啊,我上网找到一些宾馆,我来打印出来
Hey, Bongo. Come here.
嘿,Bongo.过来
You want a treat?
要点心吗?
Hey, Mike, where do you keep the dog biscuits?
嘿,MIKE, 你把狗饼干放哪了?
I'm sorry, what?
对不起,什么?
Oh, never mind.
哦,没事.
We'll just find them ourselves, huh?
我们不是刚刚找到它们吗?
We're going to find them ourselves.
我们正要去找它们
I'm sorry, Susan. I couldn't hear you. What'd you say?
对不起,Susan.我听不见你讲什么?你说什么?
Nothing.
没什么
It's not important.
不重要
It's  my tile guy. Here, see what looks good.
这是我的瓦工.这里,看看有什么好的
Hey, Phil.
嘿,Phil
Um, no, no, tomorrow morning I'm making a lumber run.
哦,不,不,明天早上我会做个木材活动
It's no good.
那不好
Uh, nope, I'm gone tomorrow night, too.
哦,不,我明晚也要走
I could let him in.
我可以让他进来
No, that's okay. Thanks.
不,可以了,谢谢
No, it's fine.
不,没事!
Just give me the key.
只要把钥匙给我就行了
I'll be around all day.
我会一整天都在的
All right, um, thanks.
好的,谢谢
Phil, I'll give a key to my, uh, neighbor.
Phil,我要把钥匙给我的, 恩, 邻居
She'll be here to let you in.
她会在这让你进来的
Like every city, Fairview had a neighborhood that was less than desirable.
像每个城市一样,Fairview也有个不是很令人满意的地方
It was an accepted fact anyone who lingered there after midnight was usually up to no good.
谁都知道午夜过后在街上闲逛的人一般都不是好人
Rex and Bree Van De Kamp were no exception.
Rex和Bree Van De Kamp也不例外
You really think this is going to work?
你真认为这有用?
This is the most impoverished neighborhood in the city.
这是这市里最贫困的地方了
Trust me, somebody will steal the car.
相信我,有人会把车偷了的
How can you be so sure?
你怎么能这么肯定
Because I have faith in the poor.
因为我相信穷人
She's so beautiful.
她真美
I shot this last year on her birthday.
去年她过生日的时候我拍了这个
How are you going to do it?
你怎么做的?
I made contact with her at a bar.
我跟她在酒吧里碰了面
She thinks I'm a real estate developer.
她认为我是个房地产开发商
Is she going to suffer?
她会痛苦吗?
No.
不会
Edie Britt will disappear, and you'll go back to your life.
Edie Britt会消失的,而你也会回到你原来的生活
Before you do it,
在你做之前
do you think you could ask her why she sent this note to my wife?
你认为你可以问她为什么她把这个留言给我妻子吗?
You can't think like that, Mr. Young. You can't give in to your curiosity.
你不能那样想,Young先生,你不能对你的好奇心让步
Curiosity leads to guilt.
好奇心导致愧疚
Guilt leads to talking.
愧疚让我们说话
You still have questions?
你还有问题吗?
I want to be clear about something --
我想知道一些事情
I walk away with this cash, it's done.
我拿走了这些钱,用光了
No refunds, no buyer's remorse.
没有退的,没有买家会自责
I get it.
我知道了
We won't talk again, so I'll ask one more time.
我们不会再谈了,所以我要再问一次
Are you sure you want this?
你确定你要?
My wife is dead because of Edie Britt.
我妻子因为Edie Britt而死
I absolutely want this.
我非常想
You've been awfully quiet.
你一直安静的可怕
I've just been...
我一直....
thinking about the kids.
在想孩子们
They sure grew up quickly, didn't they?
他们真的成长的很快,对吧
They sure did.
他们当然了
I remember telling them when they were babies that they weren't allowed to get any bigger
我记得当他们还是小孩的时候 我告诉他们,他们是不会长大一点的
because they were so adorable,
因为他们是那么可爱
and we were so happy.
我们也很开心
Yeah, well...
是啊...
they sure didn't turn out like we expected them to.
他们没有向我们期望之外的地方发展吧
No.
没
They didn't.
他们没有
We could have been better parents.
我们可以是更好的父母
We weren't that bad.
我们没那么糟
We still have so much to teach them.
我们还有很多要教他们的
For starters, we need to get across to Andrew the enormity of what he's done.
作为开始,我们必须让Andrew 理解他所做的是多么大的罪恶
I-I suppose we could punish him.
我想我们可以惩罚他们
All right, well, what's the appropriate punishment for a child who drives over a woman?
是啊, 对于一个撞到一个女人 的孩子什么惩罚是恰当的呢?
I-I don't know.
我,我不知道
You know no matter how the kids turn out, I still love them.
你知道无论孩子们变成什么样,我都爱他们
Of course you do.
当然了你会的
But I'll never forgive them for growing up so quickly.
但是我永远不原谅他们这么快的长大
Hey. Look.
嘿,看
And then I opened the cabinet, and there was all this money in it.
然后我打开橱子,里面都是钱
I mean, there was wads of it.
我的意思是,有很多卷钱
That's why you're freaking out?
这就是为什么你这么反常吧
A few stacks of cash? Come on.
一小堆钱?好了吧
Well, what? Realistically, I've known this guy a few weeks.
好吧,什么?实际上我认识这人才几星期
I mean, he could be a hit man for the mob.
我的意思是,他有可能是一群暴徒里的杀手
If you really think that, why are you going on a trip with him?
如果你真这样想,为什么你还要跟他一起去旅行？
I never get out of the house.
我从未离开过这个房子
Mom, if you really need something to freak out about,
妈,如果你真的需要一些可能反常的东西
just remember you're going to spend the night with Mike in a hotel.
只要记得你跟MIKE在旅馆呆了一晚上
No man has seen you naked in years except your doctor.
这些年来除了你的医生没有男人看见过你的裸体
Yeah, and he retired. I try not to take that personally.
是啊,而他退休了,我试着不让那变成私人的
You look old in that.
你穿那个很老
Oh.
哦
Maybe I am being silly.
可能我有些傻
But going to a hotel with a man is a big deal to me.
但是跟一个男人去旅馆对我来说是件很大的事
What if Mike is hiding something?
如果Mike隐瞒了一些事怎么办?
Like what?
像是什么?
I don't know.
我不知道
That's dad.
那是爸爸
I got to go.
我要走了
Now,  listen to me.
现在,听我说
No more freaking out. I need this weekend to go well.
没有更反常的东西,我需要这个周末来变好
Why do you care so much?
你为什么担心这么多?
Because I'm going to have a husband of my own someday,
因为我有天要拥有一个自己的丈夫
and I really don't want you living with us.
而且我真的不想你和我们住一起
Are the lady fingers okay?
这位小姐的指头还好吗?
Oh, they're terrific.
哦,惨不忍睹
We just appreciate y'all stopping by.
我们感激你们都来拜访.
Well, we just wanted you to know how much we care.
恩,我们只是想你知道我们有多担心
So have the police come up with any leads?
警察有提出什么线索吗?
Not really.
不一定
They'll be able to determine the make and model of the car,
他们可以决定车的模型和材料
but without any eyewitnesses, no one seems very optimistic.
但是没有目击者就很不乐观了
Well, more importantly, is there any good news about Juanita?
恩,更重要的事,有没有Juanita的好的消息?
No change.
还是没变化
All we can do is wait and hope for the best.
我们现在能做的只有等待和希望最好的
We put her on our prayer list at church.
我们把她放到我们教堂的祈祷者名单
Oh, that's very sweet, Danielle. Thank you.
哦,那太贴心了,Danielle,谢谢
It must really help during times like these --
这种时候有这个真的很有帮助
having kids.
有孩子
Yeah, they're a blessing.
是啊,他们是个祝福
Children make everything worthwhile.
孩子们让一切都变的有价值了
You guys are the future.
你们是未来
Legacy.
遗产
Thanks.
谢谢
After we're all dead, you'll be the only ones left to carry on.
等我们都死了,你会变成唯一一个要坚持的人
Gabrielle and I are about to start a family.
Gabrielle和我要组成一个家庭
Oh, hey, that-- that's great.
哦,嘿!那,那很好啊
When did you decide this?
你什么时候做的决定?
It's a fairly recent development.
是最近的一个重大发展
I see.
我知道了
We'll talk about this later.
我们晚一些再讨论这个
Face it,
面对它
we're shallow people.
我们是浅薄的人
I mean, can our lives have any meaning if all we ever do is buy stuff?
我的意思是,如果我们一直做的 只是买东西 我们的生活还有什么意义?
That depends on what we buy.
那取决于我们买什么
I want a child.
我想要个孩子
In case you've forgotten, before we got married, we made a deal.
以防你忘了,在我们结婚之前,我们达成个协议
No kids.
没有小孩
Yeah, well, deals were meant to be renegotiated.
好吧,协议会被重新商量
Well, we're not negotiating my uterus.
恩,我们不能和我的子宫谈判
We should probably be going.
我们应该走了
Yeah. Mm.
是的,恩...
Thank you so much.
非常感谢
That was weird.
那很怪
I feel awful for Carlos.
我觉得Carlos可怕
That talk about children is obviously coming from his grief.
关于孩子的谈论明显来自他的悲痛
Whatever.
无论怎样
I'm off the hook.
我解脱了
A weary Lynette drank her potent tea in hopes of finally finding the sleep that had eluded her.
疲倦的Lynette希望喝了她的 灵药她就能最终找到躲避她的睡眠
Unfortunately for Lynette,
不幸的是Lynette
there would be no rest for the weary.
没有休息
Go to hell.
去死吧
Go to hell, go to hell, go to hell, go to hell, go to hell.
去死吧去死吧去死吧去死吧去死吧
Sorry we're late. Kenny Litman couldn't find his neckerchief.
对不起我们迟了,Kenny Litman找不着他的手帕
Come on, guys.
快来啊
Lori Jean, the scout meeting is today?
Lori Jean,侦察会议是今天?
Mommy.
妈
What? Oh.
什么？哦
Right. Okay, boys.
恩,好的,男孩们
This knot is called the bowline.
这个结叫帆脚索
It is a remarkably useful knot.
这是个非常有用的节
Now, pick up your ropes.
现在,拿起你们的绳子
Okay, first, we cross this end over here,
好的,首先,我们在这交叉这个根部
and then we make a loop,
然后我们打个环,
and then another loop,
再是另一个
and then you sort of pull it through, I'm guessing,
然后你们差不多就会了,我想
and then you just -- ready?
然后你们就可以--准备好了?
Yank it taut.
猛地拉紧
Mommy, that doesn't look like the picture.
妈,这跟图上的不太像
You're never going to be a sailor. What do you care?
你又不会去做水手,那么担心干吗?
Okay, everybody, let's just take a break.
可以了,大家,休息一会
Thanks.
谢谢
Okay. It's all up there.
好的,那都在上面了
Can I get a signature?
我可以要个签名吗?
Oh, of course.
Oh, 当然.
Thank you very much.
非常感谢.
Here you go.
给你
Have a nice weekend.
祝你有个愉快的周末
You too, lady.
你也是,小姐
Hey, ma'am! You still here?
嘿,女士,你还在这吗?
I forgot to give you a receipt!
我忘了给你一个收据!
Ma'am?
女士？
Hello?!
你好?
I need help! I'm up here!
我需要帮助,我在楼上
I'm trapped in the floor! Hello!
我被困在楼梯里了,喂!
If you came in here to judge me,you can just leave.
如果你过来是评判我的话,你可以走了
Wait! Wait! No.
等等,不
Wait. Don't -- don't go. Wait, I have an idea.
等等,别, 别走. 我有个主意
Here, here, here.
这,这
Here. Grab the towel, Bongo.
这,抓住毛巾,Bongo
Come on, grab the other end.
过来，抓住另外一端！
Good boy.
好孩子
That's it. Get the other end.
就是那样，抓住那一端
Come on, Bongo!
加油，Bongo!
Pull the other end! Come on, Bongo!
拉那头！加油！Bongo!
What are you doing? Bongo, over here!
你在干吗？Bongo，在这啊！
Bongo?
Bongo？
Oh --oh, don't do that. Oh, Bongo.
哦哦，别那样！哦，Bongo!
While Susan remained hopelessly stuck,
当Susan还是那样没有希望的样子时
Gabrielle was moving to confront the issue of her young lover's restless conscience...
Gabrielle到了面临她的年轻情人 的不安的良心的时候...
Nobody's home.
没有人在家
I know. I've been watching.
我知道,我在看着呢.
I came to talk to you.
我过来跟你谈谈
Although she would need to be discreet.
虽然她需要小心谨慎.
Keep working.
继续工作
What were you thinking, showing up at the hospital?
你在想什么,干吗在医院出现?
I had to see if she was okay.
我必须知道她是不是还好
You need to keep a low profile right now.
你现在要低调一点
Look... you and I are finished.
你和我结束了
From now on, I'm sticking with Danielle.
从现在开始,我要和Danielle一起坚持
Why would you say that?
你为什么说那个?
I hate myself for what we did.
我为我们做的事憎恨我自己.
Okay, I can't sleep at night.
我晚上睡不着
I've got to make a clean break.
我要有个清净的休息.
We weren't driving the car.
我们没有开车
We didn't chase Juanita into the street.
我们没有在街上追Juanita
She wouldn't have been there if we weren't having an affair.
如果我们没在一起,她也不会在那
Oh, for god's sakes, between you and Carlos...
哦,行行好,你和Carlos
listen to me carefully. You didn't do anything wrong.
仔细听我说. 你没做错任何事.
That's not what Father Crowley thinks.
Crowley神父不是那样认为的
What?
什么?
I went to confession.
我去忏悔了
Have you lost your mind?
你疯了吗?
What did you tell him?
你告诉他什么了?
Everything.
所有的事
Including...
包括...
in the alley behind the truck stop?
在卡车站台后面的小巷?
Everything.
一切
Oh, damn you.
哦,去你的
What is wrong with you?
你哪儿出毛病了?
Lassie would have had a fire truck here by now,
现在Lassie这会有个救火车
you stupid dog.
你这个笨狗
Good boy, Bongo!
好孩子,BONGO!
Run, Bongo, run! Go get help!
去啊, Bongo,去! 找人帮忙!
Andrew, um...
Andrew.恩...
I know the last few days have been stressful, and, uh...
我知道过去的几天里压力很大,而且,恩...
you know, if you ever need to talk to anybody...
你知道,如果你需要和什么人谈谈...
I know, I know. You and dad are here for me.
我知道,我知道,你和爸爸会在这的.
Actually, I was thinking we could arrange for you to talk to a professional.
事实上,我在想我们应该让你去和一个专业人士谈
A shrink?
神经科医生?
You think I'm crazy?
你认为我有问题?
Of course not.
当然不
It's just that the accident probably stirred up a lot of emotions,
那只是一个事故激起的很多情绪
and it would be normal for you to be feeling confused or depressed or ashamed.
感到困惑难过或是惭愧的对你是正常的
I'm cool.
我很冷静.
Um, really.
恩,真的
Honey, you put a woman into a coma.
亲爱的,你把一个女人弄的昏迷.
Surely that arouses some kind of emotion.
当然了那引起了一些情绪
Yeah, well, it doesn't.
是啊,对,但没有
Now, if you'll excuse me...
现在,如果你觉得对不起我...
No, I won't. Not until you tell me.
不,我不会,直到你告诉我.
Why do you care?
为什么你要担心?
Because I need to know that you're not a monster.
因为我必须知道你不是个魔鬼.
You want to know how I feel?
你要知道我怎么想的吗?
Yeah.
是
Okay, here goes.
好的,现在开始
I feel bad that she got hurt,
我觉得难过她受伤了
but I also feel bad that my car got dinged
但是我还觉得我的车被污染了
because somebody didn't have enough sense to look both ways before she crossed the street.
因为有些人对他们过马路时 没有向两边看的足够的意识
And I also feel bad that now I'm going to have to ride my bike to school.
而且我还觉得我要骑车上学很难过
Andrew, you almost killed another human being.
Andrew,你几乎杀了人
She's an old lady, okay?
她是个老女人,好不好?
She's lived her life.
她有自己的生活.
I have my whole life ahead of me, and now it might be screwed up.
我前面有我的整个人生而且现在我需要振作
That's what you should be worried about.
那就是你需要担心的
What I'm worried about, Andrew, is that you don't seem to have a soul.
我担心的是,Andrew,你看起来没有良心
Give me one good reason why I shouldn't call the police.
给我个理由为什么我没有打电话叫警察
Because I'm your son.
因为我是你儿子
That would make you the monster.
那就是让你有个魔鬼的原因.
Hey, buddy.
嘿,小狗
Susan, is that you?
Susan,是你吗?
Mike? I'm upstairs... sort of.
Mike? 我在楼上...差不多
Hang on. I'll -- I'll be right up.
等等,我,我正要上去
What happened?
发生什么事了?
Well, see, this bird, um...
好,看这只鸟,恩....
flew in your bathroom window,
从你的洗手间飞了近来
and I tried to save it, but, uh...
我想救它,但是....
it died.
它死了
I don't think that's what happened.
我不认为是那样发生的
I don't think so, either.
我也不认为
Can you just help me get out of here, please?
你能不能帮我从这出去?
Come on.
来
Thank you.
谢谢
You have no idea what that was like.
你不知道那像什么
You went through my cabinets.
你看了我的橱子
What?
什么?
Oh, I can explain that.
Oh,我可以解释
Get out of my house.
出去!!
Mike
-
Get out.
出去
Hello there.
你好
Good afternoon.
下午好
Oh. Well, isn't this just as pretty as a picture book.
哦,好啊,这是不是像本图画书那样漂亮?
Well, the plan is to put in a small condo.
好了,计划是盖座小公寓楼.
You want to make some money, or you want to pussyfoot around?
你想赚钱吗?又或者你想走走?
What do you suggest?
你认为呢?
I'm thinking strip mall.
我在想那条林荫路.
I've run some numbers.
我在那跑过很多次
Nice stationery.
漂亮的信纸
Oh, it's stolen.
Oh, 那是偷来的
What do you mean?
你什么意思?
After my house burned down, I was staying with this neighbor Martha Huber.
在我的房子被烧掉之后, 我就和邻居Martha Huber住
That is, until the old troll threw me out.
直到那条老鱼把我赶出来
Anyway, I'd steal her stuff, she'd steal mine.
无论如何,我偷了她的东西,她也偷了我的
It's the circle of life.
那是生存循环
So this paper is hers.
所以这纸是她的?
Oh, god, yes.
哦,上帝,是啊
No, Tom, you can't do this to me.
不,Tom, 你不能这样对我
Because I need you home.
因为我需要你在家
Boys, stop it! I am on the phone!
孩子们,停止!!!我在打电话!!
Well, yeah, I-I realize it's not your fault that the meeting got postponed,
好啊,是,我想,会议延期不是你的错,
but you promised you'd be back tonight.
但是你答应过今晚回来的
I-I-I got to go. The kids are --
我我要挂了,孩子们...
yeah, I know you're sorry.
是啊,我知道你很抱歉
Just will you try and get back as soon as you can?
能不能就试着尽早回来?
Okay. Bye.
好的,再见.
Boys, would you please, please stop it?
孩子们,可不可以,停止啊!
Really, really, mommy's got a headache, okay?
好的好的,妈妈头疼,好吗?
Just -- ugh.
只要,恩
turn that damn thing off!
把那个该死的关掉
What's the matter with you?!
你们出什么毛病了?!
Why won't you listen to me?!
为什么你们都不听我的话呢?
You want noise?!
你们要噪音吗???
What?
什么?
I just came over to say I'm sorry,
我只是过来说我很抱歉
and I'll pay for all the damage.
弄坏的我会付钱
Don't worry about it.
别担心..
Well, so...
好的,所以...
in your mind, I-is the date off?
你的意思是,约会取消了?
Well, you snooped around my house and went through my stuff.
你巡视我的屋子还检查我的东西.
Yeah, in my book, that's pretty much a deal breaker.
是啊,在我的字典里,漂亮女人是祸水
Hold on a minute.
等等
Now, I started snooping around
现在我开始巡视了
because I found all that money by accident,
因为我无意中发现钱
and then I found a gun.
然后发现了一支枪
Are you a drug dealer or something?
你是毒犯或者是什么?
Is that what you think?
那就是你认为的?
Well, I wouldn't know, because you never let me in.
恩,我怎么会知道,你从来不让我知道
You know, there's this whole part of your life that you keep completely walled off.
你知道,你把你整个生活都封闭了
I have a gun for protection. I keep cash for emergencies.
我有枪为了保护我自己,存钱来应急
I'm a good guy,
我是个好人
Susan, and you should know that.
Susan, 你必须要知道.
I'm -- I'm not obligated to share every little detail of my life with you.
我,我不能把我生活的每一个小细节都跟你分享.
Well, every little detail is one thing.
每个小细节都是一件事啊.
You know, weird, creepy secrets, that's another.
你知道,很奇怪,小秘密,那是另外一种
I don't want to be with somebody who doesn't trust me.
我不想和不信任我的人在一起
Well, maybe we shouldn't be dating.
恩,我们可能不应该约会
Maybe we shouldn't.
可能我们是不应该
Do you mean that?
你认真的吗?
Yeah.
是的
Well, I hope that your, you know, little secret keeps you warm at night,
恩,我希望你的,你知道,小秘密可以让你在夜里温暖
because you're throwing something really great away to protect it.
因为你扔掉了一些重要的东西来保护它.
Susan, you got to take my kids for a while.
Susan, 你能帮我看一下孩子吗?
Lynette, this just really isn't the time --
Lynette, 现在真不是时候
no, no, I'm sorry, but I can't do this.
不,不,对不起,但我做不了
It's just --it's too much.
那只是,只是太多了
Boys, you stay with your aunt Susan.
孩子们,你们要和Susan阿姨呆一会.
Lynette, you know, when are you coming back?
Lynette, 你知道,你什么时候回来吗?
Lynette?!
Lynette!
There's Lynette's car. She's got to be close.
那是Lynette的车, 她被关在里面了
I hope the kids aren't too much for Danielle to handle.
我希望对Danielle来说孩子们不是太难搞定.
She'll be fine.
她会好的.
What do you think's happening with Lynette?
你知道Lynette出什么事了吗?
I don't know, but I'm scared.
我不知道, 但我很怕.
Something's very, very wrong.
有些事真的很不对劲.
Lynette, honey?
Lynette, 亲爱的?
Are you okay?
你还好吗?
Father.
神父
I'm -- I'm so glad you could come and pray for mama.
我,我很开心你会来而且为妈妈祈祷
Please, sit, sit.
请坐,做
Thank you, Gabrielle.
谢谢,Gabrielle.
Listen, since you're here,
听着,自从你在这儿
there's something I've always wondered about.
有些事我真的很想知道
That whole thing about priests not being allowed to repeat what they hear in confessions --
整件事是牧师们不被允许重复他们所听到的忏悔词..
is that a hard rule or just a general guide line?
是一个艰难的角色又或者只是个总的指引线路?
Rest assured, everyone's secrets are safe.
放心,每个人的秘密都是安全的
That's good to hear.
听到这个太好了.
I'll keep yours, too, if you want to talk.
我也会保守你的,如果你要说的话
Oh, me?
哦,我?
No, no.
不,不
Confession's not really my thing.
忏悔真的不是我的事
That's a shame.
那是个可耻的事
Okay, you can stop condemning me with your eyes.
好了,你可以停止用你的眼睛谴责我了.
Right now.
现在
I know you know about the affair,
我知道你知道我的事
but you know nothing about my life.
但是你对我的生活一无所知
Look, it's not even an issue anymore. John and I are finished.
瞧,那甚至不再是一件事了,John和我结束了
Gabrielle, the church is pretty clear on this.
Gabrielle, 教堂是很纯洁的
If you commit a mortal sin and you die without repenting,
如果你犯了不可饶恕的罪你会因为没有忏悔而死的
you go to hell.
你会下地狱
Well, aren't you just a ball of fun.
好啊,你难道只有找乐子的胆啊
So if I confess, it'll clean the slate, right?
所以如果我承认了,那就会了结往事,对吗?
Not only that.
不止那样
If you want god's forgiveness, you have to be truly sorry,
如果你要上帝的原谅的话,你就得真的感到抱歉
and you have to promise not to commit the sin again.
而且你还得保证不再犯
So what happens if I repent later,
如果我忏悔的晚些会怎么样?
like, say, when I'm 75?
像是,我75岁的时候说
I wouldn't recommend waiting. What if you die before then?
我不建议等待,如果你在那之前就死了呢?
Well, let's say I don't die.
恩,就想我不会死
I do yoga, I eat well.
我做榆枷,我吃好的
If I wait, does my repenting still count?
如果我等,我的忏悔还有效吗?
If you mean it, yes.
如果你真的想,是的
Thank you, father Crowley.
谢谢你,Crowley神父
You have been a tremendous comfort.
你是个很好的安慰者
Um, I will let you do your thing.
恩..我会让你做些事
Gabrielle.
You know, we're all responsible for the choices we make.
你知道,我们对我们做的选择有全部责任
Don't you want to be a good person?
你真的想做个好人吗?
What I want is to be happy.
我想做的只是快乐
That's the answer of a selfish child.
那是个自私小孩的答案.
I know.
我知道
Then I started taking the pills because they gave me energy,
然后我要开始吃药因为它给我能量.
but then I couldn't sleep at night,
但是我那之后睡不着
and I was getting so tired in the daytime,
然后我在白天就很累
and it totally messed me up.
那真的让我很乱
I love my kids so much.
我很爱我的孩子
I'm so sorry they have me as a mother.
我很抱歉他们有我这样一个母亲
Lynette, you are a great mother.
Lynette, 你是个伟大的母亲.
No, I'm not.
不,我不是
I can't do it.
我做不到
I'm so tired of feeling like a failure.
我不想再有作为一个失败者的感觉
It's so humiliating.
那是很羞耻的
No, it's not.
不,它不是
So you got addicted to your kids' A.D.D. medication.
你对你孩子的A.D.D药物治疗上瘾了.
It happens.
它发生了
You've got four kids. That's a lot of stress.
你有4个孩子,那是很大的压力.
Honey, you just need some help.
亲爱的,你只是需要一些帮助.
That's what's so humiliating.
那就是很羞耻的
Other moms don't need help.
别的母亲不需要帮助
Other moms make it look so easy.
别的母亲看起来很容易
All I do is complain.
我所做的所有事就只是抱怨.
That's not true.
那不是真的
When -- when Julie was a baby,
当,当Julie还是个小孩的时候
I-I was out of my mind almost every day.
我每天几乎快要失去理智了
I used to get so upset when Andrew and Danielle were little,
我经常很不安当Andrew和Danielle都很小的时候
I used their nap times to cry.
我在他们睡午觉的时候哭
Why didn't you ever tell me this?
你们干吗从不跟我说这个?
Oh, baby.
Oh, 宝贝
Nobody likes to admit that they can't handle the pressure.
没有人愿意承认他们不能搞定压力
I think it's just like we think, you know,
我想那就是我们认为的,你知道
it's easier to keep it all in.
把它藏起来会容易些
Oh, we shouldn't.
哦,我们不应该
We should tell each other this stuff.
我们应该告诉彼此这件事
It helps, huh?
有帮助,对吗?
Yeah.
是的
It really does.
真的有.
So it was Martha Huber all along.
所以Martha Huber一直一个人.
Seems so.
看起来是
Edie didn't move in with Huber until after your wife received the blackmail note.
在你妻子收到这个黑色邮件之前 Edie都没有和Huber一起住
My god. We almost killed an innocent woman.
天啊,我们几乎杀了一个无辜的女人.
Like I said, I don't do refunds,
就像是我说的,我不会退钱的
but if you'd like,
但是如果你希望
I'm willing to pay Mrs. Huber a visit.
我会付钱参观Huber夫人的
No. Just keep the money.
不,留下钱
This whole thing's been tearing me up --
整件事要把我撕碎了
the nightmares, the guilt.
噩梦,自责
This isn't what Mary Alice would have wanted.
这不是Mary Alice真的要的
What would she have wanted?
那她要什么?
Answers.
答案
Hello, Mrs. Huber.
你好, Huber夫人.
Paul.
Let me give you a hand.
让我帮你一把
That's really not necessary.
真的不需要
I insist.
我坚持
Ants, huh?
蚂蚁,啊?
Yes. I've had a little infestation problem.
是的,我有一个小小的害虫问题
I wanted to take care of it before I left on my trip.
我想在我去旅行之前解决掉
Never had a problem with ants.
从未有过蚂蚁的问题
Mary Alice and I had these little black flies once.
Mary Alice和我有过一些黑色的小苍蝇
Oh?
哦?
She was so funny about it.
她对那的的反应很滑稽
She ran out and bought herself a can of poison something to spray them down,
她跑出去买了一罐毒药准备朝它们喷
so she's taking aim at one on the counter, and she just,
她瞄准一个在柜子上的目标,仅仅
stops, puts the can down.
停了一下,放下了罐子
Couldn't do it.
她做不到
She told me later it felt too personal.
她后来私下里告诉我
She truly couldn't kill a fly.
她连只苍蝇都不敢杀
That's how gentle she was.
那就是她有多温和
Then you must have lived with quite a few flies.
然后你们就必须和很多苍蝇生活在一起
I'm going to have to say good night to you now, Paul.
我要和你说晚安了,Paul
What are you doing here?
这是干什么?
I want to know why.
我想知道为什么
I know you've got a lot of questions,
我知道你有很多问题
and I also know I don't want to lose you,
而且我也知道我不想失去你
so ask me anything you want.
所以问我任何事你想知道
You just told me everything I need to know.
你只要告诉我所有我要知道的事
All right.
好吧
My idiot husband died and left me with a worthless pension.
我的白痴丈夫死后留给我 一个没有价值的退休金
I was desperate for money,
我不顾一切的想要钱
and it's better to take it from a bad person than a good one.
最好的办法是从个坏人手上弄到而不是一个好人
How was I supposed to know she'd shoot herself?
我怎么知道那会使她开枪打她自己?
She was a good person.
她是个好人
A good person who leaves her child motherless?
一个好人会留着她的孩子不管吗?
Read the bible, Paul. Suicide's a big no-no.
读圣经吧,Paul,自杀是个很不应该做的事
Don't you feel any remorse what so ever?
你难道从来不觉得自责吗?
Why should I?
为什么我要?
Your wife didn't kill herself because I wrote a note.
你老婆不是因为我写这个条子而自杀的
She killed herself because of  what she did to that poor baby.
她自杀是因为她对她的孩子所做的事
But rest assured,
但是放心
I'm praying for Mary Alice.
我正在为Mary Alice祈祷
After what she did, she'll need all of our prayers.
在那之后,她需要我们的祈祷
There is a widely read book that tells us everyone is a sinner.
有一本流行的书告诉我们每个人都是罪人.
Of course, not everyone feels guilt over the bad things they do.
当然了,不是每个人看了这书都对他们所做的坏事感到愧疚
In contrast, there are those who assume more than their share of the blame.
相反的, 有些人认为那应该比应受的谴责更多
There are others who soothe their consciences with small acts of kindness...
还有些人用他们善意的小事安抚他们的良心
or by telling themselves their sins were justified.
或者告诉他们自己他们的罪行是正当的
Finally, there are the ones who simply vow to do better next time
最后,有些人会发誓下一次会做好些
and pray for forgiveness.
然后为了饶恕而祈祷
Sometimes their prayers are answered.
有时他们的祈祷被回应了